All right, let's go.
We'll split up here.
Okay.
We have at least three intruders
who have defeated Terada and Koyama.
It's finally time for you,
the Awakened, to shine!
I'm sure that you have all
endured rigorous training.
And now it's time to show them
how powerful we can be!
Yeah!
Though... you probably
don't stand a chance.
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
We'll be able to find our answers
1%, 2%, 3%, 4%, 5%, 6%, 7%, 8%, 8%, 10%...
11%, 12%, 13%, 14%, 15%,
16%, 17%, 18%, 19%, 20%...
21%, 22%, 23%, 24%, 25%...
Admiration, troubles, pump up
26%, 27%, 28%, 29%, 30%...
Searching for yourself, telepathy
31%, 32%, 33%, 34%, 35%...
Asking for the impossible, psycho punch
36%, 37%, 38%, 39%, 40%...
Youthful Salt Splash
Mob? Mob? What do you want?
Mob? Mob? Why do you want?
Mob? Mob? Who do you want?
Move! Move! Just like Mob!
If everyone is not special
Maybe you can be what you want to be
Even if you hold onto happiness and sadness
Your life is your own, OK?
It's OK you are not special
We'll all be able to find our answers
81%, 82%, 83%, 84%, 85%,
86%, 87%, 88%, 89%, 90%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"Mob Psycho 100" 91%, 92%, 93%,
94%, 95%, 96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
91%, 92%, 93%, 94%, 95%,
96%, 97%, 98%, 99%...
"The Heinous Aura"
"~Mastermind~"
All the Scars were sent after the intruders?
This must be a huge deal.
Just how long will we have to
be babysitters or errand boys?
Let it go, man.
Those of us who don't awaken
will always be stuck at the bottom.
Eventually, we'll end up
subordinates of kids like him.
Speaking of kids,
did you hear about the kid
who was sent from HQ as a temp?
Apparently he's an Awakened Child
created by HQ.
What? Are you saying a normal kid survived
that insane awakening experiment?
Man... I want to be
in an experiment at HQ, too.
Don't even think about it. You'd die.
It does much worse things than
just destroy your mind.
You know about HQ, Gen-san?
Just stories.
I heard that it's so painful
that people have even died.
After spending twenty years
as a lackey in this organization,
I've learned that HQ is bad news.
Er... What the hell
do you think you guys are doing?
Busted, huh? Should've known.
--What happened to your trainers?!
--Took them out.
I can't believe they lost to some kids.
-We'll--
--Don't even think about it!
Gen-san? Why?
Huh, that's unexpected. Are you sure?
Yeah. Go.
Well, thanks.
We won't get stabbed in the back, will we?
Gen-san, why?!
Shut up, you young'uns!
You don't know anything!
A powerful esper and a normal
human are like night and day.
The difference in strength is astronomical.
It's not one versus ten,
it's zero versus ten.
There's no way you can win.
Damn it... If only I'd awakened...
Give it up.
If you don't awaken the first time,
there's no hope.
Huh? Seriously?
Are we going to be lackeys forever, then?
You're okay with that, Gen-san?!
See? You really don't get it.
Claw will definitely reign over this world,
and even us lackeys will be rewarded.
Right now, we just have
to wait and endure...
...until the day of the revolution.
Oh? Oh, oh, oh?
Looks like I found a rather special door.
Maybe it's where they're keeping
Ritsu and the others.
I thought it was an intruder,
but it's just security.
What are you wandering around for?
Well, I just got a little lost.
I have a terrible sense of direction.
Do your damn job.
Yeah, sorry.
I actually haven't been in this room yet.
Maybe I'll just have a peek...
Stop.
You're an impostor, aren't you?
I'm telling you to let me see the room,
small fries.
He's one of the intruders!
All of you, release your powers!
Whoa. Individually, they're small fries,
but they're not bad when they work together.
A normal human wouldn't be able to get free.
You wanna keep this up until you pass out?
But in the end...
...you guys still reek of small fry!
So, let's see...
...just what's in this room...
Hey, explain.
Th-This is the awakening experiments room...
These look like torture devices.
Th-They said that experiencing pain
is one way to be awakened...
Hmm... They're not too far off.
But, even after going through all that pain,
all you guys can do is momentarily
paralyze someone as a group.
The world really does favor the gifted.
You guys have a better chance
focusing on body building.
Oh?
It's not every day a ghost wanders in here.
Why don't you become mine?
I'll take good care of you...
"'Claw' Upper Echelon: Matsuo"
You want to own me?
Someone dangerous just showed up...
Say what? You didn't
find them in their cage?!
Don't mess with me!
I told you to bring them here!
Er, but you see...
It appears they got out on their own.
I'll kick yer ass if yer talking out of it!
I-I'm not lying.
I see.
Good grief.
I don't like imitating them,
but it seems to work well on weaklings.
You underestimated us.
You're wide open! Ignite! It lit!
With this flame, I'll defeat y--
I can't believe you thought
you could fight me with that.
Man, everyone in Claw seems a bit--
Did you get burned?
This is true pyrokinesis,
the ability to wield fire.
"'Claw' Upper Echelon: Miyagawa"
--A Scar...
--Are you the brat Koyama was talking about?
All right.
I'll turn you into ash.
"My barrier can hold up," is what
you're thinking, isn't it?!
The inside of your barrier turns
into an insanely hot sauna,
so much so that your lungs
will burn when you breathe.
It's a stupid error that amateurs make.
You're the amateur.
Well, aren't you a spirited one?
But to fight back,
you'll have to drop your barrier,
and then you'll be burnt to a crisp.
And if you keep this up, you'll be steamed.
That means this fight is over.
Your options are burn to death
or swear fealty to me--
Just try it.
As you wish!
You fool! Now I won't spare you,
even if you beg and cry!
But I guess this heat would
evaporate your tears, too!
Ouch. When I switched it over,
my clothes got singed.
It's true that you can't defend and attack
at the same time with psychic powers.
So then, you just have to put up a barrier
around the source of the fire.
But... I guess you're not listening.
You're causing a racket, so I'll free you.
Well, this is surprising.
You can still move with those burns?
Perhaps people with pyrokinesis
have a higher tolerance to heat.
Though, well...
...your lack of flexibility
was your downfall.
I win.
Wow, now I'm sweating.
--Maybe I was a little scared.
-- I praise you.
You're stronger than I was as a child,
but I'm stronger now than
you will be in ten years.
Give up now.
Oh, come on. Quit exaggerating.
"Mob Psycho 100"
Oh, hello. Good evening.
Um, I'm looking for my younger brother,
and apparently he's
somewhere in this building.
Found him! My dolls found an intruder!
"'Claw' Upper Echelon: Mukai"
Hey, Tsucchi. Can I do
whatever I want with him?
Yeah. He's your toy now.
"'Claw' Upper Echelon: Tsuchiya"
Yay!
I'm gonna go have a look!
If I don't hurry,
my dolls will break him in a jiffy.
The puppet master, Mukai.
Quite the ability she's got.
She can remote control
all of those wooden dolls,
meaning she holds an
immortal army in her hands.
Look at her, so excited over
finding a new toy.
I definitely don't want
to get on her bad side.
They went past.
All right, let's go.
We have to find the exit quickly.
Ah. Found the escapees!
--That was easy!
--Sorry, I picked the wrong route.
You did just fine.
We're going to force our way through.
Don't look down on us, brat!
Fly away! Combination Super Psychokine--
Wow...
It looks like their espers
aren't that strong.
They're all on par with Hoshino-kun.
--What does that me--
--They'd be scarier using their bare hands.
Not bad. It's true that those guys
are still useless as soldiers.
"ShO" Not bad. It's true that those
guys are still useless as soldiers.
Not bad. It's true that those guys
are still useless as soldiers.
I don't see a scar like
the trainers mentioned on him.
He's not a part of the upper echelon.
--Who are you?
--Gee, I dunno. Who could I be?
And now we get to deal
with someone annoying.
We're in a bit of a hurry right now.
You can quiz us some other time.
Don't be so mean.
I thought we could be friends.
Th-This guy's dangerous.
We're finished...
All of you, go ahead.
--Kageyama...
--I'll take care of him.
Wait! He's too much!
You can't beat me, no matter what you do.
I don't believe that.
Why? It's not like you're dumb, right?
I don't know. Maybe it's because
I know someone stronger than you.
I see. So he must be one of the intruders.
Then, I guess I'll just have to use you
as bait so I can meet him.
Tsucchi!
Oh, Mukai.
You're back already?
I see you're as ruthless as ev--
Wood scraps?
Mukai, what happened to your dolls?
He broke all of my dolls!
Leave this to me.
Hey, you.
Are you the intruder?
He really is just a kid.
A kid like this...
Are you violent, too, old lady?
Who are you calling old?!
--Tsucchi!
--You're not going to stop me with telekinesis like that!
--You're not going to stop me
with telekinesis like that!
Her ability is hardening gigong,
which she uses to divert all of her qi
into her fists or knees to
make them more powerful.
In terms of pure fighting ability,
she's top-class, even within the Scars.
If she happens to lose,
Takeuchi-kun, you might
actually have to get serious.
"'Claw' Upper Echelon: Takeuchi" Takeuchi-kun,
you might actually have to get serious.
Takeuchi-kun, you might
actually have to get serious.
It'll be troublesome if
I let him use telekinesis.
It's not having much effect.
Is his qi guard really thick?
Without any build up?!
Hey! Your phone's ringing!
What a surprise.
You came this far, so why are you crying?
Why do I have to beat up a lady, too?
--Huh?
--What did you say?
My master said
that guys who hit women
are the biggest losers in the world.
You're quite the gentleman,
but that's an insult.
I want to fight you fair and square.
Don't hold back, and come at me!
Stay away!
Looks like I drew the short straw.
I've never even heard of this.
This human actually made
evil spirits his obedient pets.
You're good at running away.
But why don't you leave that body behind?
Isn't it easier to run away
in your spiritual form?
Are you holding him hostage?
He's not worth it.
Crap!
This body won't hold up much longer.
Only third-rate spirits would let
the body they possessed be damaged.
But I have even less of a chance
beating him in spirit form.
In that case...
What are you trying to do?
Those things return to
their master after they attack.
I wonder why they're trained to do that.
Maybe it's because the master
can't protect himself!
I see right through you!
--He's fast!
--Cookie! Gum-chan!
Now he can't come any closer.
What?!
He fell?
No, wait!
We can fight some other time. See ya.
I'll crush you next time.
A... After him!
He will be mine!
I'm right above you, dumb-ass.
Man, I can't believe you fell for that.
Crap! Come back!
Three seconds is plenty of time.
Better grit your teeth!
You're the one who underestimated me.
Who said I only had two evil spirits?
You mean all of those
around his waist are...
Crap! There's nowhere to ru--
Tsuchiya-san was defeated.
Takeuchi-kun, I'm counting on you.
Very well. No one is a match
for my super gigong.
I'll win, no matter what!
His face changes when he's in battle mode.
Takeuchi the super gigong user...
Even I can't completely read him.
What do you think?
I think you should all hurry up and run.
--Why?
--Because I know Kageyama-kun.
--Oh?
--Not to mention, it's impossible to take over the world with psychic powers.
Why don't you use this opportunity
to wake up from your dream?
You won against Miyagawa.
What are you doing with the normals
when you're so powerful?
We are special beings.
And that's reality, not a dream.
As long as you believe that,
you'll never be able to defeat him.
I know you were trying to do something,
but I'm really sorry.
I'm in a hurry right now.
Y-You're kidding...
Is that Ritsu?
Why?
He's still breathing. Thank goodness...
But why?
Why does Ritsu have to go through this?
My little brother...
Unforgivable.
Oh? What's this situation?
Have you already been defeated
before I even used my powers, boy?
Did you do this?
You're not hiding your hostility at all.
Then I'll show you even greater
despair, free of charge.
No...
This isn't real...
"Rejection”
Man, that was close.
He managed to amplify the illusion
Muto showed him and reversed it.
I'm not sure if that was planned,
or just his natural instincts.
He's pretty interesting, too.
It was totally worth using
his brother as bait.
They're great brothers.
Out of the eleven Scars,
seven have been defeated.
How should I explain that to the boss?
What's going on?
Kageyama-kun lost?
It can't be.
The guy who carried those two here...
Did he actually...
What's up? Don't be scared!
There's no way he'd lose
to someone like that!
I'm back! Oh?
I see you captured the other intruders, too.
You look happy.
Yes. One of the intruders was
an evil spirit with a very strong ego.
Dimple-kun, too?
This poison jar has hundreds
of evil spirits thrown in.
The one that survives after they devour
one another becomes the ultimate pet.
What is this place?
Wait, stop...
We can talk this out!
W-Wait, even if you eat me,
I have no nutritional value!
Help me!
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light.
The dreams and ideals that we believe in
Feel like they may shatter
as soon as we take our eyes off them
Thousands, millions of distinct Flashbacks
Underneath the sky in slow motion,
So real that I want it to disappear.
My heart was stolen
a second before the unpredictable,
After being hurt on a whim
something from somewhere
is overflowing and won't stop.
We, who live at the corner of the world
Will get beyond our tears
and head towards the light
Zero, or One? Ten, or Hundred?
We're looking for the answer.
But over and over again
The sound in our hearts resonates together
"Yes n "No n
I see it. There's the exit!
Now we can call for help!
Wait, stop! It's no use.
What's wrong, Hoshino?
Damn it. We're not going
to be able to get through.
--Wait, that's...
--What the...?
Did someone important
show up or something?
That aura...
Even I can feel it.
It's an insanely powerful esper!
No, it can't be.
Th-Then the only possibility is...
Could he be this organization's...
...Claw's boss?!
The boss of Claw finally shows himself.
Yes, it's me.
I'm sorry I kept this hidden
from you so long, Mob.
No matter what happens from now on,
live your life to the fullest.
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Episode 11:
"Master
"~Leader~."
"Master"
"~Leader~"
"Master” "~Leader~" The serious
option C? An excellent decision.
"Master"
"~Leader~"